Guide to the Wanda M. Corn Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Wanda M. Corn papers
1970-2006
SC0822
Corn, Wanda M.
7 Linear feet
Papers include correspondence, memoranda, reports, publications, newsletters, minutes, and other materials pertaining to her teaching and administrative duties in the art department, her involvement with the Stanford Humanities Center, and other aspects of her professional life, 1970-2006; and as acting director of the Stanford Museum, 1987-92. Other items of note include newsletters and other records from the College Art Association of America, 1970-91; and newsletters and other materials from the Women's Caucus for Art, 1972-90.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Accession 2006-132 is open for research. The following items have been removed for restriction:
Box 7 1996-97: Search for Early 20th C. Europeanist.
Box 7 SHC Director Search Committee - 1984
Box 7 Museum: Hilarie Faberman
Box 7 Museum: Assistant Curator Search
Box 7 Museum: Staff
Box 7 Search Associate Director - SHC
Box 7 Charles Junkerman
Accession 2008-107 is restricted.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Wanda M. Corn, a scholar of late 19th- and early 20th-century painting and photography, joined the faculty of Stanford's Department of Art and Art History in 1980. She is the author of THE GREAT AMERICAN THING: MODERN ART AND NATIONAL IDENTITY, 1915-1935 (1999) and several exhibit catalogs including GRANT WOOD, THE REGIONALIST VISION (1983) and THE ART OF ANDREW WYETH (1973).
Description of the Collection
Papers include correspondence, memoranda, reports, publications, newsletters, minutes, and other materials pertaining to her teaching and administrative duties in the Department of Art and Art History, her involvement with the Stanford Humanities Center, and other aspects of her professional life, 1970-2006; and as acting director of the Stanford Museum, 1987-1992. Other items of note include newsletters and other records from the College Art Association of America, 1970-91; and newsletters and other materials from the Women's Caucus for Art, 1972-1990.
Access Terms
College Art Association of America.; Corn, Wanda M.; Iris & B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts at Stanford University; Stanford University. Department of Art and Art History.; Stanford University. Humanities Center.; Women's Caucus for Art.; Art --Study and teaching.; Art--History--Study and teaching.; Stanford University--Administration.; Stanford University--Faculty.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Papers, Accesion ARCH-2006-132
  - Department
    - Department: 1990-91 Operating Budget (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Department: Programs and Lectures (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Department: New Voices Lecture Series 1993-94 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Department: Innovative Academic Courses (SWOPSI) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Department: Development, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4A)
    - Comprehensive Exams in Art History (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Department: Course Offerings (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Linda Poolaw Project (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Department: Stanford Graduations (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Department: Stanford in Washington (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Department: Studio Meetings and Minutes (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Department: Summer Session (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Department: Teaching (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Department: Art History Meetings and Minutes (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Department: Lecture Series 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Dept [assorted memos, calendars, course lists, correspondence, etc.] 1996-97 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Department: Undergraduates (memos) 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Department of Art, Stanford (memos, minutes, correspondence, etc.) 1981-88 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Teaching (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Teaching Assistants, general info, 1990-91 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Department: Undergrad Advisees, 1995-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Art Department [overlarge folder of memos, correspondence, etc., with DVD of opening gala for Stanford Humanities Center 2001], 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Grievance transferred to Box 8, Folder 2.
    - Department: Art History Meetings and Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Restricted until September 1, 2066.
    - Department, 1982-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Restricted unilt September 1, 2062.
  - Slides (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Women At Stanford (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Arts Program Chair, Stanford [not a search file], 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Copyright Information (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Censorship (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Board of Trustees (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minority Issues / Affirmative Action, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    includes "Toward Multiculturalism: A Guide to Recruiting and Enrolling Targeted Minority Students in Master's and Ph.D. Programs at Stanford University" and the 1987-88 Affirmative Action Report for Graduate Studies
  - American West Program Stanford, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee: H and S Faculty Council, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Senate, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - PPB [Planning and Policy Board of the Academic Council], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Faculty Club (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Jeanne Kennedy Dinner (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Graduation Stadium (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Alfred Frankenstein Memorial Lectures (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Feminist Studies - Stanford (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Research Funds (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Stanford Quad Restoration, 1983-86 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    [includes Ray Koskovich's "Saving the Olmsted Plan" 1983 report to the Board of Trustees
  - American Studies (memos, reports), 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bob Byers (correspondence re gift of Benjamin West paintings with slides) 1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Institute for Research on Women and Gender (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Collectors - American Art (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Humanities and Special Programs, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Pioneer Mother, correspondence re possible acquisition of A. Phimister Proctor sculpture with slides, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Humanities Study Group, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Gorbachev at Stanford, 1990-05-04 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Think Again Stanford, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - AID and COMFORT [booklet from benefit concert for people fighting AIDS 1990] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Decoupling (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Museum
    - Museum: Anderson (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Museum: AOA [African and Oceanic Art] (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Museum: Carol Memos (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Museum: Centennial Exhibition New York, 1992-02 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Museum: Centennial Exhibition (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Museum: Centennial Handbook (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Museum: John and Mary Collier Exhibition (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Museum: Committee for Art (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Museum: Charles Cowles (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Museum: Development, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Museum: Earthquake Preparedness (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Museum: John Eastman, correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Museum: Education (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Museum: Exhibitions (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Talks: Fundraising, Museum, MFA, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      includes exhibit publication "Stanford Artists in New York" Autumn 1987 Charles Cowles Annex Gallery
    - Museum: Marcia Growden (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Museum: Nathan Cummings Foundation (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Museum: 100th Birthday Celebration, 1991-05-14 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Museum: Stanford Collects Exhibition (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Museum: Scully/Sultan exhibition, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Museum: Students [contains only Daily article on the Museum], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Museum: Vision Statement I, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Museum: Vision Statement II, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Museum: Visiting Committee (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Wanda - N.Y. Trip Fall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Museum: Budget, 1989-90 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Museum: Barbara Morgan Exhibition (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Museum [over-large file of correspondence, memos, etc.] (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Stanford Museum (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Museum, correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - CAA
    - CAA [College Art Association] Newsletter, 1976-1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - CAA Board of Directors, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - CAA, 1970-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - CAA Nominating Committee, Committee - Status of Women, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Professional Ethics CAA (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Distinguished Teaching CAA Award, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - CAA Nominations Board of Directors (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - CAA San Francisco, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Humanities Center
    - Stanford Humanities Laboratory, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Joseph Brodsky, visit to Stanford Humanities Center, 1992-10 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Stanford Humanities Center, memos, correspondence, etc., 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Fundraising - SHC (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Restricted until September 1, 2070.
    - SHC (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Humanities Center, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Directorship - SHC (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Advisory Board, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - SHC Farewell Events (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Re: Humanities Center (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Painting in the South [planning for an exhibition, not at Stanford], 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Prospects; An Annual Journal of American Cultural Studies – correspondence 1984-86 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dunlap Society, 1981-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - KQED (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Quarterly (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kress Foundation, 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - California Arts Council (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - General - Art Commissions (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - California Art Commission, 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Advanced Placement (Educational Testing Service), correspondence and publications, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NAA [New Art Association] newsletters, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - WCA [Women's Caucus for Art] newsletters and newsmagazine, 1972-1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Women's Caucus + Other Early Women's Organizations (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Floor Plans - Dept. of Art History [scheme for Old Chem building], 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Papers and Various Correspondence, 1998-2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - H and S – Hewlett [needs assessment reports] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Historic Values Subcommittee, Stanford Buildings, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - American Studies, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lectures - Stanford (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - C-Library, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Advisees – Undergraduate (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Needs Assessment Spring, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - American Studies - Stanford (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Outdoor Art, correspondence, memos, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Meeting Notes, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Film Studies (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - DLCL [Division of Literatures, Cultures, and Languages] Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Research (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - New Mail to Process (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Cultural Nationalism Conference (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Djerassi Foundation (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - John Cage at Stanford, 1992-01 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Rutgers Folder - Humanities fellowships info and misc. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Finance / Donations Processing (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Multi Cult. - Dept. of Art (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Expanding American Art History to Reflect Multiethnic Diversity (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Studio Art Program Report (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - “Budget” (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Studio Art Evaluations and Recommendations (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Women's Issues at Stanford (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Class Info (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Department Memorandums (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meetings 1/3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meetings 2/3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meetings 3/3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Re: Museum of Art (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Personal / Biographical (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Suzanne, 1984-1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Additional Papers, Accesion ARCH-2008-107
  The materials in boxes 1-7 are restricted. Box 8 is open for research use.
  - Departmental Files
    - Department of Art & Art History Newsletter (2 copies), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Memorial card - Michael E. Moors (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Memorial program - Michael Edward Moors, 2001-10-14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Henry Luce Foundation, Inc. Evaluation of Arts Grants, 1993-08 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Phillips Gallery Study Center Proposal, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Museum: Director Search Vol. I (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Department: Americanist Search, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Department: Americanist Search, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Women’s Faculty Caucus (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Department: Studio Search (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Contract & Appointment, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Museum: Director Search Vol. 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - ABD Study, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Loose Materials (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wolf CV + Dissertation List (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Americanist Search, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Eng. Dept Americanist Search, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Department Visiting Faculty, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Department: Grad Student Affairs, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Department Lecture Series, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Department: Associate Chair Affairs (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Department: Paolo Berdini [Empty] (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Department: Info Resources Specialist [Empty] (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Department: Misc Office Supplies/Equip (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Deans: Teaching Awards [Empty] (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Department Modernist Searches, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - [UNLABELED] (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Department: Art I Dedications (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Department: Art 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - C.V.’s & Photos (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Vital Statistics II, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Stanford in DC, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Vital Statistics I, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Deans (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Sylvia Wohlmut (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Department: Artist Search, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Letters of Appreciation (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Art Library (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Art Spaces (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Department: Lisa Bloom (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Centennial Weekend, 1991-09 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Department: Christensen (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Department: Christensen Lecturers (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Department: Committee on Visual and Computer Resources (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Department: Dean Matters (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Leah Dickerman (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mona (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Eitner Memos (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Elsen Memos (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - L. Eitner Retirement Celebration, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Department: Faculty Members (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Department: Faculty/Staff Salary Guidelines (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Department: David Hannah (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Inspirational Speeches (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Department: Memorabilia (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Nemerov (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Department: Michael Marrinan (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Department: Richard Randell (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Department: Replacement Teaching (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Department: Retreat, Fall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Department: Slide Librarian (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Hunk Anderson Collection (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Department: Slide Librarian Search, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Department of Art & Art History Newsletter, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Henry Luce Foundation Biennial Report, 2002/2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Department of Art & Art History Publication, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Department of Art & Art History Newsletter, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Course Offerings, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Others Syllabi II (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Revisions to Graduate Program (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Staff, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Gift Funds (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Department: Betsy Gates Fund (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Chair Stuff, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising - Art Gallery, etc. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Dept. Review (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Department (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Loose Materials [Miscellaneous] (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Loose Materials [Miscellaneous] (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Loose Materials [Miscellaneous] (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Loose Materials [Miscellaneous] (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Art of America (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - The Art of America, Appendix to Proposal Narrative (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - The Art of America (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - The Fund for Arts and Sciences Films, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - The Art of America (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Djerassi Resident Artists Program Annual Report, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Djerassi Resident Artists Program, Annual Report, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Syllabi – Feminism + Women’s Art (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Other Teachers’ Syllabi I (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Department of Art and Art History at Stanford University Newsletter, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University Department of Art and Art History Graduate Student Handbook (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University Department of Art and Art History Graduate Student Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Teaching Art History: A Sourcebook for TAs (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - [Correspondence] (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Department of Art and Art History Annual Review, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Stanford University Report of the Commission on Graduate Education 2005 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Deeply Anonymous Donor (DAD)
      Restricted 75 years from date of creation.
      - Loose Materials [Miscellaneous] (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Margaretta Lovell (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - DAD Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Dell Upton (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Aldona Jonaitis (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - DAD Budgets & Progress Reports (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - 1996-97: Postmortem Forum 10/26/96 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - May 5th – 6th – Symposium (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Material / Immaterial Bodies Symposium April 9-10 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - The Grossness of Thomas Eakins’s Gross Clinic (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - 1996-97 1930’s Symposium May 1-3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - 2001 Symposium: The Everyday and the Extraordinary Dell Upton (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - DAD General (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - DAD Bryan Wolf (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - DAD Selection Committee (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Drawing Connections Symposium (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - DAD Sally Stein (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - DAD Roger Stein (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Rick Powell (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Sarah Burns (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Paul Staiti (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Elizabeth Johns (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Study of the American West (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Object Inside Event Program (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Slides
      - Lipchitz Installation (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Segal (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Segal, Damaged Gay Liberation statue (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Confidential (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Posters
      - The Everyday: The Ordinary and the Extraordinary, 4 and 5 May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Mind the gap: ON the Modernist Divide in American Art/History, April 16-17, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Poster: “Is There Life After the Humanities Center?” (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Djerassi Resident Artists Program, 1995 Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Art History Student Files, 1981-2008
    - Sample Proposals (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Sample C.V.’s (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Department: Prospective Graduate Students (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - [Unlabeled] (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Undergraduate Art History Program (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Tom Hertenstein (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Student Art History Program (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Students (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 2/94 Grad Selection (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Undergrad Advisees (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Laura Barnebey (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Denise Barney (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Peter Blank (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Emily Blanchard (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Lisa Bloom (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Boswell, Peter (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Jennifer Borland (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Brown, Bill (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Mary Campbell (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Cateforis, David (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Collins, Barbara (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Melanie Corn (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Jill Dawsey (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Miguel DeBace (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Dennis, Susan (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Keith Eggener (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Evans, Carlton (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Merrill Falkenberg (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Martin Fox (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Jeannie Fraise (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Karen Fraser (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Michael Gaudio (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Amanda Glesmann (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lela Graybill (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Evelyn Hankins (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hutchinson, Elizabeth (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hutton, Molly (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Carrie (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Joseph, Brandon (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Aaron Jue (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Carolyn Kastner (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Joni Kinsey (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Sarah Koehler (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Kupperman, Laura (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Lambert, Carrie (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Tirza Latimer (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Leggat, Graham (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Rael Lewis (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Annelise Madsen (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Beth Mangini (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Judy Maxwell (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - McDonnell, Patricia (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Meyers, Michelle (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Cynthia Huong (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Confidential – Cynthia Huong (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Nora Niedzielski-Eichner (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Maria Ochoa (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Ortel, Jo (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lisa Pasquariello (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Perry, Claire (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Robbie Reid (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ross, Janice (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Rust, Marion (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Rob Savoie (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Emily Shapiro (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Schwain, Kristen (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Shaw, Gwendolyn (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Louise Siddons (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cherise Smith (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Jill Steinberg (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Kirsten Swinth (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Teagle, Rachel (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Todd, Ellen (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Wayne, Ken (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Weems, Jason (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Wellman, Sherry (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - John Weiland (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Whiting, Cecile (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Susee Witt (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Sylvia Wohlmut (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Wright, Lesley (Box 6, Folder 25)